Hello, Logan. Congratulations.
>> Thank you so much.
>> Um, can can you go back in time a little
bit? You go to Iowa as a defensive
tackle and then you switch to the
offensive line center. Can you take us
through that that transition and when
did it take you like when was the moment
you felt like center would work for you?
>> Yeah, you know, those first couple
years, you know, I transitioned uh in
22, so right before spring bowl,
um, right after our center had left that
year. And you know, I had to fill some
shoes. Um, and it was very humbling. You
know, those first couple years, uh, for
sure, especially as an offensive line
group, we weren't very good. Uh, but,
you know, that class, we stuck together
and worked. Um, and it just started with
the leadership in that room. And I was
just so grateful, you know, for coach
Barnett for sure, my offensive line
coach at Iowa, just him. And, you know,
I I it took some time. And, man, I I
still feel like I haven't even played my
best football yet. Um, and I haven't
figured it out. So, you know, it's it's
been a journey, but I think, you know,
the past two years for sure is when I
realized that, you know, if I really
wanted this, I just got to go out there
and take it.
>> Kevin Fishbane.
>> Hey, Logan. Congratulations. Welcome to
Chicago.
>> Um,
>> what do you know about Ben Johnson and
what he likes uh from the center
position? Obviously, we all know that he
loves the offensive line, but what have
you gotten to learn about him and and
what that means to him? Yeah, I know he
he loves to run the football, especially
outside zone, which is awesome. You
know, that's exactly what how I've been
taught and what we did. Um, and you
know, meeting with him, uh, he he likes
to put a lot on the center's plate,
which is awesome. You know, playing
center, uh, it's your job to to get
everybody, um, in order and know what
they're doing. You know, whether it be a
combo or pass pro, whatever it might be,
they put a lot in the center. So, it's
definitely going to be challenging, but
I look forward to it. Uh, and it's going
to be a lot of fun for sure.
>> Courtney
Logan, congratulations. I know you said
you don't feel like you've even like
scratched the surface. Um, you know,
paraphrasing your words there, but you
did win the Remington Award. How did you
go from being such a raw prospect at
Planning Center to being the nation's
top center?
>> Just the guys I had around me.
Absolutely. I was very fortunate to play
with some studs, man. Um, you know, that
that whole offensive line, I was just
surrounded by a bunch of good players.
uh and the way they approached
everything they did, you know, practice,
uh meetings, you know, the way they
showed up in the building, you know,
without the guys I had around me, you
know, that award u I would have never
received it. And I know they like to say
it's an individual, uh award, uh but
it's just as much theirs as it is mine.
So, yeah, I couldn't have done it
without him.
>> And I mean, the lineage that Iowa has in
the league of putting out a lot of good
offensive linemen, what kind of pride do
you take in that of being the next part
of that group?
You know, I take a lot of pride um you
know, just playing under coach Fence
who's an offensive line guy and coach
Barnett. Uh you look at the guys who
have come out of Iowa and you know, they
come back in the offseason and train
with us too. So I get to, you know, ask
them questions. Uh which is just so cool
all the way back from like Robert
Gallery. Um just a bunch of dudes who
who do it the right way and love Iowa
and you know they're better people than
they are football players, which is
awesome. and to be able to talk to them
and learn from them and to carry on the
tradition truly is something special.
>> Dan,
>> Logan, how do you describe the strengths
in your game?
>> Yeah, you know, I I think one thing for
sure, and you know, I'm not perfect at
it, uh, but communication is huge,
especially at center, right? just
talking and communicating, getting guys
on the same page, and even if you know
I'm wrong, at least I'm communicating
loud and making sure we're all on the
same page and we're wrong together. I
think that's something a center has to
be good at and, you know, something I'll
continue to get better at. Um, and
something I look forward to, especially
going into this offense, Coach Johnson's
offense, uh, and learning that. So,
it'll be a lot of fun and definitely a
challenge.
>> Last one, Adam.
Log Logan, two quick questions for you.
C. Can you take us through uh all all
the the pre-draft contact you had with
the Chicago Bears quickly and then one
more after this?
>> Yeah. So, uh at the combine had an
informal meeting with them and then uh I
had a a 30 visit uh gez however long ago
now. Uh
>> sorry.
>> Okay, there you go.
Can you hear me?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Just meeting with everybody like
it just felt like home. Uh the people
there um it just felt like they truly
loved it. And being in Chicago and you
look at a place like Chicago, the
history there and being able to be a
part of that. Uh it still hasn't really
set in for me. You know, just got
drafted over long ago. So, I'm still
trying to get used to it. Um but man, it
truly is a special place and it starts
with the people you have and you know, I
I know it's going to be a great place.
And then the last question for you is
how much do you like ketchup because I
think Hines 57 is about to give you a
lifetime supply as the 57th pick.
>> Oh, I love it. I love it. I'll take as
much as I can get. So, uh, that is
awesome. That is really cool.
>> Did you Did you know that?
>> I had no idea.
That is crazy.
>> I think there's some endorsements coming
your way.
>> Oh, there you go. Let's go catch up.
>> Awesome. Thank you so much, Logan. Thank
you guys.